enrollapp.com 2019-03-27

# Enroll | Improve the Web

### Enroll Privacy Policy

Effective as of May 22, 2018

#### At Enroll, we’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This Policy explains when and why we collect personal information about people who visit our website, how we use it, the conditions under which we may disclose it to others and how we keep it secure.

We may change this Policy from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you’re happy with any changes. By using our website, you’re agreeing to be bound by this Policy.

Any questions regarding this Policy and our privacy practices should be sent by email to [privacy@zurb.com](mailto:privacy@zurb.com) or by writing to ZURB, Inc, 100 W. Rincon Ave, Campbell, CA 95008.

#### Who are we?

We’re Enroll, a firm dedicated to helping make the web a better place. We connect website/application creators to users and potential users through our design testing and survey platform, Helio.

#### How do we collect information from you?

We obtain information about you when you use our website, for example, when you contact us about products and services, or register for an account.

#### What type of information is collected from you?

The personal information we collect might include your name, address, email address, PayPal email address for payment, IP address, and information regarding what pages are accessed and when, among other information. You make the decision whether to proceed with any activity that requests personal information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however, you may be unable to use our services.

##### Here is a full list of personal data that we collect.

  * Name
  * Email address
  * PayPal email address
  * Computer Experience
  * Time Online
  * Gender
  * Location
  * Birth Date
  * Education
  * Phone number
  * Income
  * Timezone
  * Industry
  * Occupation
  * Job Title
  * IP Address

We use this information to match you with and send you relevant tests from Helio. Your information is anonymized and segmented as demographic data ("Panelist Data"), for access to our [Helio](https://helio.app/) users.

We will never share with them your Personally Identifiable Information ("PII"):

  * Name
  * Email address
  * PayPal email address
  * Phone number
  * IP Address

**NOTE: This does not stop[Helio](https://helio.app/) test creators from asking for this information directly. You may refuse to take any test that you do not feel comfortable taking.**

#### How is your information used?

We may use your information to:

  * Set you up with an account at [enrollapp.com](https://enrollapp.com/)
  * Send you relevant tests from our testing platform, [Helio](https://helio.app/).
  * Notify you of changes to our service.
  * Send you communications which you have requested and that may be of interest to you. These may include additional testing opportunities outside of [enrollapp.com](https://enrollapp.com/).
  * Manage the performance or our Platform.
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with our Platform.
  * Develop new products and services
  * Providing customer support
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support, administrative messages, and promotional email.

We review our retention periods for personal information on a regular basis. We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long you maintain an account with us in good standing. You may request to cancel your account at any time, at which point we will permanently remove your information from our system.

#### Data Accuracy

We wish to maintain accurate information and our goal is to provide a means of contacting us should you need to review, update or correct that information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your personal information by email to [support@enrollapp.com](mailto:support@enrollapp.com) and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your personal information that we hold as soon as practicable.

#### Age Restriction

Anyone using [enrollapp.com](https://enrollapp.com/) warrants and promises that they are 13 years of age or older. [enrollapp.com](https://enrollapp.com/) does not intend to collect personally identifying information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13 we ask that you do not use this web service.

If you reside in the European Union, you are governed by the policies of the GDPR. Under this policy, you may not use our service if you are under the age of 16 years.

#### Your Personal Information

The data we collect is used anonymously. We won’t sell personal information that links the anonymous data we collect from you. There might be one exception in the event [enrollapp.com](https://enrollapp.com/) itself is sold. In this case we would transfer your personal information to our buyers so that they could continue to provide the same great [enrollapp.com](https://enrollapp.com/) service.

[enrollapp.com](https://enrollapp.com/) may disclose to authorized law enforcement personnel the personal data from anyone who poses a threat. This might include those that are attempting to commit fraud or those who conduct activities that could bring harm to others. We assume that this is not you so please don’t worry.

#### Data Security

[enrollapp.com](https://enrollapp.com/) has a sophisticated security program intended to keep the information stored in our system protected from unauthorized access. We store your information in a secure data center located in the United States, and replicated in secure regions around the world. Here are some of the key features of our security practices:

  * All user data is encrypted at rest.
  * All user data is encrypted in transit.
  * Our service is hosted on AWS, to learn more about their security practices, visit: <https://aws.amazon.com/security>
  * Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) mitigation services powered by industry-leading solutions
  * Firewall and VPN services to help block unauthorized system access
  * User data is stored and encrypted on a network not connected to the internet.
  * Systems access logged and tracked for auditing purposes
  * All changes to user accounts are logged for auditing
  * Regular, off-premise, multi-region, backups.
  * User data is soft-deleted to protect from user mistakes. Data is permanently deleted when the account is scheduled for deletion, you can cancel your account at anytime by going to Account Settings and choosing “Cancel My Account”
  * All software dependencies are kept up to date and are patched on a regular basis.
  * Stable system updates and security patches are applied at the hardware level when they are released.
  * All user data is served over HTTPS with TLS 1.2 and TLS 1.3 with HSTS enabled.
  * Two factor authentication is available for extra security.
  * All passwords are salted and encrypted.
  * Requests to authorize users in our system are rate limited to protect from malicious traffic.
  * We do not collect credit card information.

If you are aware of any security issues with regards to our service, please report them to [security@zurb.com](mailto:security@zurb.com).

#### Data Sharing

Occasionally, we may share personal information with our selected business partners for the purpose of providing you with improved services. If you prefer that we not provide your information to our business partners, you may let us know by using one of the methods described below in this policy. We also retain the services of outside contractors to provide services for us. They may be used to provide training services, technical support, to develop improved services, to handle order processing or to perform other services. We require that these contractors keep the Personal Information of customers secure and confidential.

We provide a number of ways for you to “opt-out” of receiving additional information from us or having us provide your personal information to our partners. We may offer you these choices at the time you give us your information. Users who no longer wish to receive our promotional or transactional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to an email communication and writing “unsubscribe” in the subject line in the email or by emailing us at [support@enrollapp.com](mailto:support@enrollapp.com). You can also cancel your account on the Account Settings page.

Our Web pages may contain links to other sites. We do not necessarily share personal information with those websites and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

#### Use of Cookies

When you visit [enrollapp.com](https://enrollapp.com/) we may store information about your web session and assign you one or more ‘cookies’. Your browser will store these cookies on your computer in a small text file. For example, when you decide to login as a [enrollapp.com](https://enrollapp.com/) member, we store encrypted information in your browser so you don’t have to login on every page.

Permanent cookie files remain on your computer’s hard drive until you delete them manually using your browser or operating system software. You can enable your browser to refuse cookies, but doing so may disable access to some services and tools that we offer.

#### Data Accuracy

To the extent that you do provide us with personal information, we wish to maintain accurate personal information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting us should you need to review, update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your personal information by email to [support@enrollapp.com](mailto:support@enrollapp.com) and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your personal information that we hold as soon as practicable

#### Consent

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our [Privacy Policy](https://enrollapp.com/privacy). [enrollapp.com](https://enrollapp.com/) reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. If there are material changes to this statement on how [enrollapp.com](https://enrollapp.com/) will use your personal information, we will prominently post these changes prior to implementing them. If you use our website after we post these changes, this indicates your acceptance of them. Regardless of later updates, we will follow the privacy practices described in this privacy statement at the time you provided us with your information.

#### Data Portability

If you are subject to the GDPR, you have the right to request your data to be sent to you upon request. You may request your data by reaching out to [privacy@zurb.com](mailto:privacy@zurb.com). At which point we will email you back your requested data as a JSON file.

#### Data Removal

You may request at any time to have your account canceled. Upon cancellation, your account will be scheduled for deletion. Accounts scheduled for deletion are deleted 30 days after cancellation, in case the data was deleted in error. After 30 days, your personal data will be permanently removed from our services. Some anonymized data may be retained in Helio, and Enroll after account deletion.

If you would like to continue using our services after the 30 days, and your data has been removed, you are free to register for a new account and continue using the service.

To cancel your account, you can initiate a request in the Dashboard under Account Settings, or email us at [support@enrollapp.com](mailto:support@enrollapp.com).

#### Subprocessors

Enroll engages certain onward subprocessors that may process personal data submitted to Enroll's services. These subprocessors are listed below, as may be updated by Enroll from time to time:

Name of Subprocessor | Description of Processing | Location of Processing  
---|---|---  
Amazon Web Services, Inc. | Cloud service provider | United States  
Google Apps | Internal company infrastructure | United States  
Google Analytics | Website analytics and performance | United States  
Timber Technologies, Inc. | Log aggregation service | United States  
Honeybadger Industries LLC | Error tracking and uptime monitoring | United States  
Tilde, Inc. | Software performance monitoring | United States  
Cloudflare, Inc. | Networking and Firewall | United States  
GitHub, Inc. | Software version control | United States  
SendGrid, Inc. | Transactional mail services provider | United States  
Intercom, Inc. | Customer relationship management | United States  
Dropbox, Inc. | Corporate document storage | United States  
Docusign, Inc. | Contract signature processor | United States  
PayPal, Inc. | Payment Processing | United States  
AlertLogic, Inc. | Intrusion detection services | United States  
  
#### Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to [support@enrollapp.com](mailto:support@enrollapp.com) or visit our Help Center.
